pokedex100.com 2018-12-29

# Pokedex100 - The best Pokémon hunting platform

****

Thank you for visiting pokedex100.com. We respect and are committed to protect your personal information. Please read our policies on privacy (“Privacy Policy”) below to get a better understanding of the commitments we take to respect and protect the rights of our clients and to maintain the security of the information the clients provide to us. 

We reserve the rights to change, modify, expand and delete a part or parts of this Privacy Policy at any time by publishing such changes on this website. This document indicates that the user consents to regularly checking for updates of the Privacy Policy of Clients’ Information. If the user continues to use the website after it has been changed, it is indicated that the user has agreed to such changes. The lastest reiteration of the Policy is published at <https://pokedex100.com/privacypolicy>. 

#### Privacy

We respect the privacy of all our clients who use the website and we believe in the utmost importance of our clients’ understanding of how we collect and process their information. Please note that our website may contain links to other websites which we do not own or control. Accordingly, we cannot assume responsibility for the security of those, or any other, websites, as the risks are from the user’s access to those websites. We strongly encourage all users to check the Privacy Policies of any website they want to log on to. 

Information we collect 

We collect information to deliver better services to our clients. 

When participating in Donation Packages, the user wiÏl send us their registration email at Patreon and Discord ID. 

Information we collect from the use of our services 

We collect information on which services our clients use and how they use them. Some examples are when they use Pokémon lists, log on to websites or watch and interact with our advertisements and contents. 

Google Advertising Cookie for running advertisements, taken from <https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/1348695>

\- Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website or other websites. 

\- Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. 

\- Users may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info.) 

If you have not opted out of third-party ad serving, the cookies of other third-party vendors or ad networks may also be used to serve ads on your site, which should also be disclosed in your privacy policy in the following manner: 

\- Notify your site visitors of the third-party vendors and ad networks serving ads on your site. 

\- Provide links to the appropriate vendor and ad network websites. 

\- Inform your users that they may visit those websites to opt out of the use of cookies for personalized advertising (if the vendor or ad network offers this capability). Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of some third-party vendors’ uses of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting www.aboutads.info. 

Because publisher sites and laws across countries vary, we're unable to suggest specific privacy policy language. However, you may wish to review resources such as the Network Advertising Initiative for guidance on drafting a privacy policy. For additional details regarding cookie consent notices, please refer to cookiechoices.org. 

Contact Pokedex100 

If the user has any questions or comment on our Privacy Policy, please contact our Staff team at the Discord server Discord <https://discord.gg/pokedex100>. 

****
